<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>All Coding Actions Posts (Coding, Automation, Tools, DevOps, SEO, RPA) on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</title><link>https://codingactions.com/</link><description>Recent content in All Coding Actions Posts (Coding, Automation, Tools, DevOps, SEO, RPA) on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:24:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://codingactions.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multi Screen Resolution Test</title><link>https://codingactions.com/tools/multi-screen-test/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/tools/multi-screen-test/</guid><description>Test website on different screen sizes, Test your site at different screen resolutions &amp;amp; devices.</description></item><item><title>How to get My Public IP address Using Python</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-python/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-python/</guid><description>How to get My Public IP address Using Python In this tutorial, we will learn About External Public IP address:
What is Public IP address A public IP address is a globally unique IP address that is assigned to a device connected to the internet.</description></item><item><title>Automated Testing with Chat GPT</title><link>https://codingactions.com/automated-testing/automated-testing-with-chat-gpt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/automated-testing/automated-testing-with-chat-gpt/</guid><description>Chat GPT for Automated Testing Introduction: In the realm of automated testing, incorporating advanced technologies like Chat GPT can revolutionize the efficiency and effectiveness of the testing process.
With its language generation capabilities and natural language understanding, Chat GPT can bring new dimensions to automated testing, complementing existing tools like Cypress and Selenium.</description></item><item><title>Docker Environment Variables Explained</title><link>https://codingactions.com/understanding-docker-environment-variables/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/understanding-docker-environment-variables/</guid><description>The importance of Docker Environment Variables Understanding the Significance of Docker Environment Variables
Docker Environment variables play a pivotal role in Docker and Docker Compose. By delving into this topic, you&amp;rsquo;ll gain valuable insights into configuring your Docker images and dockerized applications effortlessly.</description></item><item><title>Best practice automation websites</title><link>https://codingactions.com/automated-testing/best-practice-automation-websites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 18:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/automated-testing/best-practice-automation-websites/</guid><description>Chat GPT for Automated Testing Practice automation websites In our journey of learning automated tests, it is crucial to have a dedicated system and application for practicing automation without affecting production systems. In this article, I will present a curated list of the top four websites that can be utilized for practicing automated tests without any impact on live production systems.</description></item><item><title>The Must-have VS Code Extension for Node.js Developer</title><link>https://codingactions.com/must-have-vs-code-extension-nodejs-developer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 13:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/must-have-vs-code-extension-nodejs-developer/</guid><description>The Must-have VS Code Extension for Node.js Developer VS Code extensions Visual Studio Code (VS Code) is a popular source code editor developed by Microsoft. It is free and open-source, and is available for Windows, macOS, and Linux.</description></item><item><title>How to get My Public IP address Using Java</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-Java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-Java/</guid><description>How to get My Public IP address Using Java In this tutorial, we will learn About External Public IP address:
what is Public IP address A public IP address is a globally unique IP address that is assigned to a device connected to the internet.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate SEO Challenges and Best Practices Guide</title><link>https://codingactions.com/the-ultimate-seo-challenges-and-best-practices-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 15:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/the-ultimate-seo-challenges-and-best-practices-guide/</guid><description>SEO Challenges and Best Practices Why SEO Optimization What Is Important? SEO (search engine optimization) is the process of optimizing a website to rank highly in search engine results pages (SERPs) for specific keywords or phrases.</description></item><item><title>Picking A Language (Java)| Selenium webdriver Java</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-3-picking-a-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 11:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-3-picking-a-language/</guid><description>Selenium Java Programming Language This post (Picking A Language) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Java .
In order to work well with Selenium you need to choose a programming language to write your automated acceptance tests in.</description></item><item><title>What Is My Screen Resolution?</title><link>https://codingactions.com/tools/what-is-my-screen-resolution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 14:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/tools/what-is-my-screen-resolution/</guid><description>An Online tool to check screen resolution of any display device.</description></item><item><title>How to test Google Analytics with Cypress</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-test-google-analytics-with-cypress/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 14:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-test-google-analytics-with-cypress/</guid><description>Google Analytics with Cypress What is Google Analytics Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. It is a free tool that helps website owners and marketers understand how visitors interact with their website, including what pages they visit, how long they stay on the site, and what actions they take.</description></item><item><title>How to Perform HTTP Requests with Axios</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-perform-http-requests-with-axios/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-perform-http-requests-with-axios/</guid><description>HTTP Requests with Axiosn What are HTTP requests ? HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol) is a protocol for sending and receiving data over the internet. HTTP requests are messages sent by a client (such as a web browser) to a server to request specific information or resources.</description></item><item><title>How to use puppeteer for robotic process automation ?</title><link>https://codingactions.com/puppeteer-robotic-process-automation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 10:44:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/puppeteer-robotic-process-automation/</guid><description>Puppeteer for Robotic Process Automation Puppeteer and Nodejs for RPA It is possible to use Node.js, a JavaScript runtime environment, in combination with robotic process automation (RPA) tools to automate tasks and processes.
One way to do this is by using an RPA tool that has native support for Node.</description></item><item><title>What is robotic process automation ?</title><link>https://codingactions.com/what-is-robotic-process-automation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 08:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/what-is-robotic-process-automation/</guid><description>Robotic Process Automation What is robotic process automation ? Robotic process automation (RPA) is a type of technology that allows businesses to automate repetitive, rules-based digital tasks that are typically performed by humans. RPA is typically implemented using software &amp;ldquo;bots&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;robots&amp;rdquo; that are programmed to mimic the actions of a human user, such as logging into an application, navigating through a series of screens, and entering data.</description></item><item><title>Defining A Test Strategy | Selenium webdriver Java</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-2-defining-a-test-strategy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-2-defining-a-test-strategy/</guid><description>This post (Defining A Test Strategy) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Java .
A great way to increase your chances of success with automated web testing is to first map out a testing strategy.</description></item><item><title>Selenium webdriver with Java: Selenium In A Nutshell</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-1-selenium-in-a-nutshell/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-1-selenium-in-a-nutshell/</guid><description>This post is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Java .
Selenium is a software robot sent from the future to help us test web applications. But keep in mind that it&amp;rsquo;s not one of those fancy shape-shifting robots than can run really fast.</description></item><item><title>Selenium webdriver with Java: Table of Contents</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-toc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-toc/</guid><description>This blog series steps through the process of writing Selenium WebDriver UI tests in Java from the first line of code through to running tests at scale in the cloud.
Selenium In A Nutshell Defining A Test Strategy Picking A Language</description></item><item><title>Automating Your Test Runs | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-15-automating-your-test-runs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 13:22:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-15-automating-your-test-runs/</guid><description>This post (Automating Your Test Runs) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
You&amp;rsquo;ll probably get a lot of mileage out of your test suite in its current form if you just run things from your computer, look at the results, and tell people when there are issues.</description></item><item><title>How to repeat a command until it fails</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-repeat-a-command-until-it-fails/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 08:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-repeat-a-command-until-it-fails/</guid><description>The Problem If you&amp;rsquo;re working on a test that intermittently fails, it&amp;rsquo;s useful to have a snippet that will run your test again and again until it fails. This is both to get to the state that it&amp;rsquo;s failing easier, and to prove that most likely, the bug is fixed (if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t fail after 5 test runs, chances are it&amp;rsquo;s no longer an issue).</description></item><item><title>Flexible Test Execution | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-14-flexible-test-execution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 22:22:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-14-flexible-test-execution/</guid><description>This post (Flexible Test Execution) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
In order to get the most out of our tests we&amp;rsquo;ll want a way to break them up into relevant, targeted chunks.</description></item><item><title>What Is My IP Address?</title><link>https://codingactions.com/tools/whatismyip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 10:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/tools/whatismyip/</guid><description>Find out what your public IPv4 and IPv6 address is revealing about you!</description></item><item><title>Speeding Up Your Test Runs | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-13-speeding-up-your-test-runs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 22:22:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-13-speeding-up-your-test-runs/</guid><description>This post (Speeding Up Your Test Runs) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
We&amp;rsquo;ve made huge strides by leveraging page objects, a base page object, explicit waits, and connecting our tests to Sauce Labs.</description></item><item><title>Running Browsers In The Cloud | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-12-running-browsers-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:22:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-12-running-browsers-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>This post (Running Browsers In The Cloud) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever needed to test features in an older browser like Internet Explorer 9 or 10 then odds are you ran a virtual machine (VM) on your computer with a &amp;ldquo;legit&amp;rdquo; version of Windows.</description></item><item><title>The Perfect SEO Optimized Article</title><link>https://codingactions.com/write-the-perfect-seo-optimized-article/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 18:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/write-the-perfect-seo-optimized-article/</guid><description>After researching your keywords and writing an article around the subject, use the SEO checklist below to optimize your article:
Bold Keyword Italicized Keyword Underlined Keyword
a. Make this a hyperlink (www.yourwebsite.com) to another page in your website Insert a picture and make sure its name and ALT tag is the keyword Make the first word in the blog post the keyword Have an H1, H2 and H3 Tag containing the keyword in your article.</description></item><item><title>Running A Different Browser Locally | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-11-running-a-different-browser-locally/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 13:42:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-11-running-a-different-browser-locally/</guid><description>This post (Running A Different Browser Locally) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
Now that we have some tests and page objects, we&amp;rsquo;ll want to start thinking about how to structure our test code to be more flexible.</description></item><item><title>SOLID Principles Simplified with Examples</title><link>https://codingactions.com/solid-principles-simplified/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 13:50:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/solid-principles-simplified/</guid><description>SOLID is an acronym created by Michael Feathers from the principles of object-oriented programming identified by Robert C. Martin (Uncle Bob).
These principles aim to make the code more readable, easy to maintain, extensible, reusable and without repetition.</description></item><item><title>Prepping For Use | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-10-prepping-for-use/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 13:42:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-10-prepping-for-use/</guid><description>This post (Prepping For Use) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
Now that we have some tests and page objects, we&amp;rsquo;ll want to start thinking about how to structure our test code to be more flexible.</description></item><item><title>Writing Really Re-usable Test Code | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-9-writing-really-re-usable-test-code/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 13:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-9-writing-really-re-usable-test-code/</guid><description>This post (Writing Really Re-usable Test Code) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
In the previous chapter we stepped through creating a simple page object to capture the behavior of the page we were interacting with.</description></item><item><title>How to get My Public IP address Using Node.js</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-node-js/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-node-js/</guid><description>The Problem An IP is short for Internet Protocol. It is used to identify computers or mobile devices on the Internet. Each device connected to the Internet has an IP address.
Ever needed to get your public IP address programmatically using Node.</description></item><item><title>Writing Re-usable Test Code | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-8-writing-re-usable-test-code/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-8-writing-re-usable-test-code/</guid><description>This post (Writing Re-usable Test Code) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
One of the biggest challenges with Selenium tests is that they can be brittle and challenging to maintain over time.</description></item><item><title>Verifying Your Selenium Locators | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-7-verifying-your-locators/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-7-verifying-your-locators/</guid><description>This post (Verifying Your Locators) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
If you&amp;rsquo;re fortunate enough to be working with unique IDs and Classes, then you&amp;rsquo;re usually all set. But when you have to handle more complex actions like traversing a page, or you need to run down odd test behavior, it can be a real challenge to verify that you have the right locators to accomplish what you want.</description></item><item><title>Writing Your First Test | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-6-writing-your-first-test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-6-writing-your-first-test/</guid><description>This post (Writing Your First Test) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
Fundamentally, Selenium works with two pieces of information &amp;ndash; the element on a page you want to use and what you want to do with it.</description></item><item><title>Anatomy Of A Good Acceptance Test | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-5-anatomy-of-a-good-acceptance-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-5-anatomy-of-a-good-acceptance-test/</guid><description>This post (Anatomy Of A Good Acceptance Test) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
In order to write automated web tests that are easy to maintain, perform well, and are ultimately resilient there are some simple guidelines to follow:</description></item><item><title>A Programming Primer | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-4-a-programming-primer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-4-a-programming-primer/</guid><description>This post (A Programming Primer) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
This section will prime you with just enough programming concepts (and how they pertain to Selenium) so you have some working knowledge and a vocabulary.</description></item><item><title>Picking A Language (Javascript)| Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-3-picking-a-language/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-3-picking-a-language/</guid><description>This post (Picking A Language) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
In order to work well with Selenium you need to choose a programming language to write your automated acceptance tests in.</description></item><item><title>Defining A Test Strategy | Selenium webdriver nodejs</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-2-defining-a-test-strategy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-2-defining-a-test-strategy/</guid><description>This post (Defining A Test Strategy) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
A great way to increase your chances of success with automated web testing is to first map out a testing strategy.</description></item><item><title>Selenium webdriver nodejs: Selenium In A Nutshell</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-1-selenium-in-a-nutshell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-part-1-selenium-in-a-nutshell/</guid><description>This post (Selenium In A Nutshell) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Node.js .
Selenium is a software robot sent from the future to help us test web applications. But keep in mind that it&amp;rsquo;s not one of those fancy shape-shifting robots than can run really fast.</description></item><item><title>Selenium webdriver nodejs: Table of Contents</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-toc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-nodejs-toc/</guid><description>This blog series steps through the process of writing Selenium WebDriver UI tests in Node.js from the first line of code through to running tests at scale in the cloud.
Selenium In A Nutshell Defining A Test Strategy Picking A Language A Programming Primer Anatomy Of A Good Acceptance Test Writing Your First Test Verifying Your Locators Writing Re-usable Test Code Writing Really Re-usable Test Code Prepping For Use Running A Different Browser Locally Running Browsers In The Cloud Speeding Up Your Test Runs Flexible Test Execution Automating Your Test Runs</description></item><item><title>About Coding Actions</title><link>https://codingactions.com/about-us/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/about-us/</guid><description>Coding Actions is a technical blog for Developers, Testers, SDET (Software Development Engineer in Test), DevOps and Content Creators to understand Coding, Testing, RPA, and DevOps concepts in a simplified way.
We mainly focus in these areas:</description></item><item><title>Disclaimer</title><link>https://codingactions.com/disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/disclaimer/</guid><description>If you require any more information or have any questions about our site’s disclaimer, please feel free to contact us by email at contact.codingactions@gmail.com .
Disclaimers for CodingActions All the information on this website – https://codingactions.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://codingactions.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>At CodingActions, accessible from https://codingactions.com/ , one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by CodingActions and how we use it.</description></item><item><title>search resultats</title><link>https://codingactions.com/search/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Terms &amp; Condition</title><link>https://codingactions.com/terms-conditions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/terms-conditions/</guid><description>Welcome to CodingActions!
These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of CodingActions&amp;rsquo;s Website, located at https://codingactions.com/ .
By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use CodingActions if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://codingactions.com/posts/automated-testing/k6/001_performance-testing-k6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/posts/automated-testing/k6/001_performance-testing-k6/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://codingactions.com/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/contact-us/</guid><description>Whether you have a question about posts, trials, need assistance, or anything else, our team is ready to answer all your questions.
We&amp;rsquo;d be happy to help you !
Name: E-Mail: Subject: Message: Send Message</description></item><item><title>Thank you for contacting us!</title><link>https://codingactions.com/thanks-for-contacting-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/thanks-for-contacting-us/</guid><description>Thanks for contacting us, we will reply to you as soon as possible.</description></item></channel></rss>