<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Java on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</title><link>https://codingactions.com/tags/java/</link><description>Recent content in Java on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:24:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://codingactions.com/tags/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to get My Public IP address Using Java</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-Java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-Java/</guid><description>How to get My Public IP address Using Java In this tutorial, we will learn About External Public IP address:
what is Public IP address A public IP address is a globally unique IP address that is assigned to a device connected to the internet.</description></item><item><title>Picking A Language (Java)| Selenium webdriver Java</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-3-picking-a-language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 11:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-3-picking-a-language/</guid><description>Selenium Java Programming Language This post (Picking A Language) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Java .
In order to work well with Selenium you need to choose a programming language to write your automated acceptance tests in.</description></item><item><title>Defining A Test Strategy | Selenium webdriver Java</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-2-defining-a-test-strategy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-2-defining-a-test-strategy/</guid><description>This post (Defining A Test Strategy) is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Java .
A great way to increase your chances of success with automated web testing is to first map out a testing strategy.</description></item><item><title>Selenium webdriver with Java: Selenium In A Nutshell</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-1-selenium-in-a-nutshell/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-part-1-selenium-in-a-nutshell/</guid><description>This post is part of a series about Selenium WebDriver with Java .
Selenium is a software robot sent from the future to help us test web applications. But keep in mind that it&amp;rsquo;s not one of those fancy shape-shifting robots than can run really fast.</description></item><item><title>Selenium webdriver with Java: Table of Contents</title><link>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-toc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 08:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/selenium-with-java-toc/</guid><description>This blog series steps through the process of writing Selenium WebDriver UI tests in Java from the first line of code through to running tests at scale in the cloud.
Selenium In A Nutshell Defining A Test Strategy Picking A Language</description></item></channel></rss>