<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Automation on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</title><link>https://codingactions.com/tags/automation/</link><description>Recent content in Automation on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 10:44:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://codingactions.com/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to use puppeteer for robotic process automation ?</title><link>https://codingactions.com/puppeteer-robotic-process-automation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 10:44:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/puppeteer-robotic-process-automation/</guid><description>Puppeteer for Robotic Process Automation Puppeteer and Nodejs for RPA It is possible to use Node.js, a JavaScript runtime environment, in combination with robotic process automation (RPA) tools to automate tasks and processes.
One way to do this is by using an RPA tool that has native support for Node.</description></item><item><title>What is robotic process automation ?</title><link>https://codingactions.com/what-is-robotic-process-automation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 08:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/what-is-robotic-process-automation/</guid><description>Robotic Process Automation What is robotic process automation ? Robotic process automation (RPA) is a type of technology that allows businesses to automate repetitive, rules-based digital tasks that are typically performed by humans. RPA is typically implemented using software &amp;ldquo;bots&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;robots&amp;rdquo; that are programmed to mimic the actions of a human user, such as logging into an application, navigating through a series of screens, and entering data.</description></item><item><title>How to repeat a command until it fails</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-repeat-a-command-until-it-fails/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 08:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-repeat-a-command-until-it-fails/</guid><description>The Problem If you&amp;rsquo;re working on a test that intermittently fails, it&amp;rsquo;s useful to have a snippet that will run your test again and again until it fails. This is both to get to the state that it&amp;rsquo;s failing easier, and to prove that most likely, the bug is fixed (if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t fail after 5 test runs, chances are it&amp;rsquo;s no longer an issue).</description></item></channel></rss>