<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coding on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</title><link>https://codingactions.com/categories/coding/</link><description>Recent content in Coding on CodingActions, Software, Automation, Testing, DevOps, RPA, Tools</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:24:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://codingactions.com/categories/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to get My Public IP address Using Python</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-python/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-python/</guid><description>How to get My Public IP address Using Python In this tutorial, we will learn About External Public IP address:
What is Public IP address A public IP address is a globally unique IP address that is assigned to a device connected to the internet.</description></item><item><title>The Must-have VS Code Extension for Node.js Developer</title><link>https://codingactions.com/must-have-vs-code-extension-nodejs-developer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 13:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/must-have-vs-code-extension-nodejs-developer/</guid><description>The Must-have VS Code Extension for Node.js Developer VS Code extensions Visual Studio Code (VS Code) is a popular source code editor developed by Microsoft. It is free and open-source, and is available for Windows, macOS, and Linux.</description></item><item><title>How to get My Public IP address Using Java</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-Java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-Java/</guid><description>How to get My Public IP address Using Java In this tutorial, we will learn About External Public IP address:
what is Public IP address A public IP address is a globally unique IP address that is assigned to a device connected to the internet.</description></item><item><title>How to Perform HTTP Requests with Axios</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-perform-http-requests-with-axios/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-perform-http-requests-with-axios/</guid><description>HTTP Requests with Axiosn What are HTTP requests ? HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol) is a protocol for sending and receiving data over the internet. HTTP requests are messages sent by a client (such as a web browser) to a server to request specific information or resources.</description></item><item><title>How to repeat a command until it fails</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-repeat-a-command-until-it-fails/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 08:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-repeat-a-command-until-it-fails/</guid><description>The Problem If you&amp;rsquo;re working on a test that intermittently fails, it&amp;rsquo;s useful to have a snippet that will run your test again and again until it fails. This is both to get to the state that it&amp;rsquo;s failing easier, and to prove that most likely, the bug is fixed (if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t fail after 5 test runs, chances are it&amp;rsquo;s no longer an issue).</description></item><item><title>SOLID Principles Simplified with Examples</title><link>https://codingactions.com/solid-principles-simplified/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 13:50:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/solid-principles-simplified/</guid><description>SOLID is an acronym created by Michael Feathers from the principles of object-oriented programming identified by Robert C. Martin (Uncle Bob).
These principles aim to make the code more readable, easy to maintain, extensible, reusable and without repetition.</description></item><item><title>How to get My Public IP address Using Node.js</title><link>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-node-js/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 12:24:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://codingactions.com/how-to-get-my-public-ip-address-using-node-js/</guid><description>The Problem An IP is short for Internet Protocol. It is used to identify computers or mobile devices on the Internet. Each device connected to the Internet has an IP address.
Ever needed to get your public IP address programmatically using Node.</description></item></channel></rss>